{
    "subject": "resource/Ellie_Darcey-Alden",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Ellie Darcey-Alden",
    "human_readable": "Ellie Darcey-Alden is named Ellie Darcey-Alden.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9791794419288635,
            "question": "Is there a nickname associated with Ellie Darcey-Alden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9761012196540833,
            "question": "What is Ellie Darcey-Alden's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9742299318313599,
            "question": "What name is used to refer to Ellie Darcey-Alden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9719582200050354,
            "question": "Is Ellie Darcey-Alden her full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9643551111221313,
            "question": "Is 'Ellie Darcey-Alden' a common name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9578084349632263,
            "question": "What are some possible origins of the name Ellie Darcey-Alden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9501309394836426,
            "question": "How is Ellie Darcey-Alden identified?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.919671893119812,
            "question": "Does the name 'Ellie Darcey-Alden' have any special meaning?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8983314037322998,
            "question": "Does Ellie Darcey-Alden use any other names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8964892029762268,
            "question": "Can we assume Ellie Darcey-Alden prefers this name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ellie Darcey-Alden is named Ellie Darcey-Alden.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5100_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Ellie Darcey-Alden use any other names?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5100_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the name 'Ellie Darcey-Alden' have any special meaning?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5100_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Ellie Darcey-Alden identified?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5100_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5100_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5100_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5100_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5100_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5100_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5100_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5100_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5100_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5100_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5100_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all the documents mention Ellie Darcey-Alden's full name as \"Ellie Darcey-Alden\". There are no contradictions or inconsistencies that would suggest otherwise. Therefore, the statement is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly refer to an actress named \"Ellie Darcey-Alden\" by name, thus supporting the triple that states her full name as \"Ellie Darcey-Alden.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}